=== PMBOK 7th: 369 trang ===

--- SCAN 40 TRANG ĐẦU (tìm TOC & cấu trúc) ---
[P001]: PMBOK® Guide – Seventh Edition | AND The Standard for Project Management | Over the past few years, emerging technology,
[P002]: 
[P003]: THE STANDARD FOR | PROJECT MANAGEMENT | and | A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT | MANAGEMENT BODY
[P004]: PMI Member benefit licensed to: Nguyen Minh Duc - 6191231. Not for distribution, sale, or reproduction.
[P005]: Notice | The Project Management Institute, Inc. (PMI) standards and guideline publications, of which | the document cont
[P006]: PMI Member benefit licensed to: Nguyen Minh Duc - 6191231. Not for distribution, sale, or reproduction.
[P007]: Preface | Each time work begins on a new edition of The Standard for Project Management and the | PMBOK® Guide, there is
[P008]: The feedback and inputs collectively emphasized four key points: | ▶ Maintain and enhance the credibility and relevance 
[P009]: Evolution of Key Changes in the PMBOK® Guide | PMBOK® Guide | Key Evolutionary Changes | Edition | 1996 • Distinguished 
[P010]: Like previous editions of The Standard for Project Management and the PMBOK® Guide, this | edition recognizes that the p
[P011]: A global community of practitioners from different industries and organizations, in different | roles, and working on di
[P012]: This systems view reflects a shift from the Knowledge Areas in past editions of the PMBOK® Guide | to eight project perf
[P013]: PMBOK® Guide – Sixth Edition PMBOK® Guide – Seventh Edition | A Guide to the Project Management The Standard for Project
[P014]: CONCLUSION | The Standard for Project Management and the PMBOK® Guide – Seventh Edition respond to all four | elements t
[P015]: Table of Contents | THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT | 1 INTRODUCTION ...............................................
[P016]: 3 PROJECT MANAGEMENT PRINCIPLES ..............................................21 | 3.1 Be a Diligent, Respectful, and Ca
[P017]: A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMENT | BODY OF KNOWLEDGE (PMBOK® GUIDE) | 1. INTRODUCTION .................................
[P018]: 2.4 Planning Performance Domain .................................................51 | 2.4.1 Planning Overview ..........
[P019]: 2.7.4 Measurement Pitfalls. ..................................................111 | 2.7.5 Troubleshooting Performance ..
[P020]: 3.5.7 Uncertainty .................................................................150 | 3.5.8 Measurement .............
[P021]: APPENDIX X1 | CONTRIBUTORS AND REVIEWERS OF | THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT AND | A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMEN
[P022]: APPENDIX X5 | RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FOR | THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT .................................227 | 
[P023]: List of Figures and Tables | THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT | Figure 2-1. Example of a System for Value Delivery ..
[P024]: A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMENT | BODY OF KNOWLEDGE (PMBOK® GUIDE) | Figure 1-1. Relationship between Project Manageme
[P025]: Figure 2-27. Dashboard Example. .....................................................107 | Figure 2-28. Information Radi
[P026]: Table 2-7. Checking Outcomes—Project Work | Performance Domain ......................................................79 
[P027]: THE | STANDARD FOR | PROJECT MANAGEMENT | PMI Member benefit licensed to: Nguyen Minh Duc - 6191231. Not for distributio
[P028]: PMI Member benefit licensed to: Nguyen Minh Duc - 6191231. Not for distribution, sale, or reproduction. | 2
[P029]: 1 | Introduction | The Standard for Project Management identifies project management principles that guide the | behavio
[P030]: 1.2 KEY TERMS AND CONCEPTS | The Standard for Project Management reflects the progression of the profession. Organizatio
[P031]: ▶ Project team. A set of individuals performing the work of the project to achieve | its objectives. | ▶ System for valu
[P032]: PMI Member benefit licensed to: Nguyen Minh Duc - 6191231. Not for distribution, sale, or reproduction. | 6
[P033]: 2 | A System for Value Delivery | The information in this section provides a context for value delivery, governance, pro
[P034]: ▶ Creating a new product, service, or result that meets the needs of customers or end users; | ▶ Creating positive socia
[P035]: System for Value Delivery | Portfolio A Portfolio B | Program N.1 | Program A.1 Program A.2 Program B.1 Projects | Proje
[P036]: External Environment | Internal Environment | System for Value Delivery | Portfolio A Portfolio B | Program N.1
[P037]: 2.1.2 INFORMATION FLOW | A value delivery system works most effectively when information and feedback are shared | consi
[P038]: 2.2 ORGANIZATIONAL GOVERNANCE SYSTEMS | The governance system works alongside the value delivery system to enable smooth
[P039]: Regardless of how projects are coordinated, the collective effort of the project team delivers the | outcomes, benefits,
[P040]: Projects need clear direction from customers and end users regarding project requirements, | outcomes, and expectations.

--- QUÉT TOÀN BỘ: Tìm dòng tiêu đề Chapter/Section ---

Phát hiện 51 điểm ranh giới tiềm năng:
  [P007] 'Preface'  >> 'Each time work begins on a new edition of The Standard for P'
  [P013] 'A Guide to the Project Management The Standard for Project Management:'  >> 'Body of Knowledge: • Introduction'
  [P014] 'The Standard for Project Management and the PMBOK® Guide – Seventh Edition respond to all four'  >> 'elements that stakeholders have emphasized in their feedback'
  [P015] 'THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT'  >> '1 INTRODUCTION .............................................'
  [P017] 'A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMENT'  >> 'BODY OF KNOWLEDGE (PMBOK® GUIDE)'
  [P017] '1. INTRODUCTION .................................................................................3'  >> '1.1 Structure of the PMBOK® Guide ..........................'
  [P020] '4. MODELS, METHODS, AND ARTIFACTS...........................................153'  >> '4.1 Overview ...............................................'
  [P021] 'APPENDIX X1'  >> 'CONTRIBUTORS AND REVIEWERS OF'
  [P021] 'THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT AND'  >> 'A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMENT BODY'
  [P021] 'A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMENT BODY'  >> 'OF KNOWLEDGE – SEVENTH EDITION .............................'
  [P022] 'APPENDIX X5'  >> 'RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FOR'
  [P022] 'THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT .................................227'  >> 'X5.1 Introduction ..........................................'
  [P023] 'THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT'  >> 'Figure 2-1. Example of a System for Value Delivery .........'
  [P024] 'A GUIDE TO THE PROJECT MANAGEMENT'  >> 'BODY OF KNOWLEDGE (PMBOK® GUIDE)'
  [P029] 'Introduction'  >> 'The Standard for Project Management identifies project manag'
  [P029] 'The Standard for Project Management identifies project management principles that guide the'  >> 'behaviors and actions of project professionals and other sta'
  [P030] 'The Standard for Project Management reflects the progression of the profession. Organizations'  >> 'expect projects to deliver outcomes in addition to outputs a'
  [P070] 'TAILORING'  >> 'Design the project devel- Each project is unique.'
  [P072] 'Tailoring the project approach to suit the unique characteristics of the project and its'  >> 'environment can contribute to a higher level of project perf'
  [P086] 'REFERENCES'  >> '[1] Project Management Institute. 2016. PMI Lexicon of Proje'
  [P091] 'Project management principles'  >> 'Q'
  [P097] 'Introduction'  >> 'This section describes important information about A Guide t'
  [P098] 'THE STANDARD FOR PROJECT MANAGEMENT'  >> 'Work in the project performance domains is guided by the pri'
  [P195] 'Section 2 – Project Performance Domains 101'  >> 'tsoC'
  [P225] 'Tailoring'  >> '3.1 OVERVIEW'
  [P225] 'Tailoring is the deliberate adaptation of the project management approach, governance, and'  >> 'processes to make them more suitable for the given environme'
  [P230] 'Tailoring engagement for the people involved in the project includes:'  >> '▶ People. This entails evaluating the skills and capabilitie'
  [P234] 'Tailoring for the organization involves adding, removing, and reconfiguring elements of the'  >> 'approach to make it more suitable for the individual organiz'
  [P239] 'Tailoring Steps'  >> '1) Select Approach'
  [P246] 'Tailoring involves the considered adaptation of approach, governance, and processes to make'  >> 'them more suitable for the given environment and the project'
  [P247] 'Models, Methods,'  >> 'and Artifacts'
  [P277] 'Section 4 – Models, Methods, and Artifacts 183'  >> 'maeT'
  [P290] 'REFERENCES'  >> '[1] Project Management Institute. 2020. The Standard for Pro'
  [P291] 'Appendix X1'  >> 'Contributors and Reviewers of'
  [P291] 'The Standard for Project Management and'  >> 'A Guide to the Project Management Body'
  [P291] 'A Guide to the Project Management Body'  >> 'of Knowledge – Seventh Edition'
  [P301] 'Appendix X2'  >> 'Sponsor'
  [P305] 'Appendix X3'  >> 'The Project Management Office'
  [P311] 'Appendix X4'  >> 'Product'
  [P321] 'Appendix X5'  >> 'Research and Development for'
  [P321] 'The Standard for Project Management'  >> 'X5.1 INTRODUCTION'
  [P324] 'Project Management Principles.'  >> 'The Introduction includes key terms and concepts associated '
  [P327] 'Glossary'  >> '1. INCLUSIONS AND EXCLUSIONS'
  [P327] '1. INCLUSIONS AND EXCLUSIONS'  >> 'This combined glossary includes definitions of terms and acr'
  [P328] '2. COMMON ACRONYMS'  >> 'AC actual cost IDIQ indefinite delivery indefinite quantity'
  [P329] '3. DEFINITIONS'  >> 'Many of the words defined here have broader, and in some cas'
  [P361] 'tailoring for project, 142 Project budget component, 62, 63'  >> 'transition, views and, 217–218 Project calendar, 192'
  [P367] 'Tailoring process, 137–145 Threshold'  >> 'initial development approach, selecting, 138 budget, 113–114'
  [P367] 'tailoring for the organization, 139–140 Throughput analysis, 105'  >> 'tailoring for the project, 141–144 Throughput chart, 190'
  [P367] 'tailoring for the project, 141–144 Throughput chart, 190'  >> 'Talent, 214 Time and materials (T&M), 191'
  [P368] 'tailoring considerations, 150 Virginia Satir Change Model, 163'  >> 'uncertainty, general, 119 Vision'
